

# ILIYA BAKTASH

## MECHANICAL ENGINEER

### **CONTACT**

in www.linkedin.com/in/iliya-baktash-626066248

Baktashiliya@gmail.com

iliyabaktash.ir

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm a B.Sc mechanical engineering student at the Iran University of Science and Technology. I have a keen interest in renewable energy systems. I have some experience in 3D modelling, Drawing, Research and Development, Solar Energy Systems, Hydrogen Production, Waste Recycling Systems and Machine learning. I am highly motivated to learn new things and work hard with others. Additionally, I can share my knowledge to others.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Iran University of Science and Technology**

Bachelor degree of Mechanical Engineering 2019/2023

## National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents

Diploma 2016/2019

### **LANGUAGES**

Persian - Native English - Advanced

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Intern | 2020

Wind Power generation and Wind turbine at Manjil Green Power generation Co

#### Intern | 2021

Wind Power generation and Wind turbine at Moshnir Power Engineering Services Co

#### Teacher Assistant | 2022-2023

Fluid Mechanic I at Iran University of Science and Technology

## Piping Engineer and Design Engineer | 2023- Present

3D modelling of Sari Waste Recycling and Separation, Conveyor Designing for Waste Separation, Piping Engineering for Waste-to-energy power plant of Sari, GD&T, Research and Development at **TTS Group** 

#### Research Assistant | 2022-2023

Machine learning application for Hydrogen production with Solar energy at **Iran University of Science and Technology** (Under Submitted)

### **REFERENCES**

Available upon request.